{"href":"\/business\/money\/covid-19-accelerates-urgency-of-people-wanting-to-retire-in-secure-countries-1.1076628","title":"Covid-19 accelerates urgency of people wanting to retire in secure countries","paragraph":"H:40 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:40 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/asia\/pakistani-police-chief-sparks-outrage-by-blaming-gang-rape-victim-1.1076293","title":"Pakistani police chief sparks outrage by blaming gang-rape victim","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/iraqis-dig-up-covid-19-dead-to-rebury-in-family-graves-1.1076901","title":"Iraqis dig up Covid-19 dead to rebury in family graves","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/sport\/f1\/lewis-hamilton-storms-to-tuscan-grand-prix-pole-position-1.1076672","title":"Lewis Hamilton storms to Tuscan Grand Prix pole position","paragraph":"Pierre Gasly was the surprise winner at last weekend's Italian Grand Prix but the Frenchman was brought back down to earth after he was knocked out in Q1. He finished 16th.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Pierre Gasly","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"last weekend's","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Italian","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"Frenchman","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"16th","entity_type":"ORDINAL"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/asia\/afghan-government-calls-for-ceasefire-as-historic-peace-talks-with-taliban-begin-1.1076423","title":"Afghan government calls for ceasefire as historic peace talks with Taliban begin","paragraph":"H:40 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:40 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/government\/dubai-issues-hundreds-of-fines-at-malls-in-campaign-against-covid-19-offenders-1.1076903","title":"Dubai issues hundreds of fines at malls in campaign against Covid-19 offenders","paragraph":"H:37 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:37 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/in-beirut-a-rescued-pelican-becomes-symbol-of-hope-in-crisis-stricken-lebanon-1.1077035","title":"In Beirut, a rescued pelican becomes symbol of hope in crisis-stricken Lebanon","paragraph":"In a country reeling from multiple crises, the fate of the gentle pelican brings joy and hope to customers, who watch him as he is hand-fed several kilogrammes of fresh fish every day. Or as he spits them out, if they are not to his taste.","entity":[{"entity_text":"pelican","entity_type":"NORP"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/beirut-port-fire-private-firms-say-lax-oversight-led-to-blaze-1.1076308","title":"Beirut port fire: private firms say lax oversight led to blaze","paragraph":"H:42 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:42 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/hamas-loses-appeal-against-eu-terror-listing-1.1076315","title":"Hamas loses appeal against EU terror listing","paragraph":"L:25 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:25 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/european-nations-welcome-bahrain-peace-deal-with-israel-1.1076927","title":"European nations welcome Bahrain peace deal with Israel","paragraph":"The praise comes just weeks after the UAE and Israel agreed to a similar deal.","entity":[{"entity_text":"just weeks","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"UAE","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Israel","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/the-americas\/us-gears-for-rising-death-toll-in-west-coast-wildfires-1.1076707","title":"US gears for rising death toll in West Coast wildfires","paragraph":"More than 40,000 Oregonians have fled their homes so far, with around half a million under evacuation warnings, Mr Brown told a press conference.","entity":[{"entity_text":"More than 40,000","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Oregonians","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"around half a million","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Mr Brown","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/in-beirut-a-rescued-pelican-becomes-symbol-of-hope-in-crisis-stricken-lebanon-1.1077035","title":"In Beirut, a rescued pelican becomes symbol of hope in crisis-stricken Lebanon","paragraph":"L:27 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:27 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/mohamed-salah-hits-hat-trick-as-liverpool-beat-leeds-united-in-seven-goal-thriller-1.1076731","title":"Mohamed Salah hits hat-trick as Liverpool beat Leeds United in seven-goal thriller","paragraph":"It took Marcelo Bielsa until he was 65 to reach the Premier League but a belated arrival made an immediate impact.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Marcelo Bielsa","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"65","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"the Premier League","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/horse-racing\/magical-gets-the-better-of-ghaiyyath-in-irish-champion-stakes-1.1076850","title":"Magical gets the better of Ghaiyyath in Irish Champion Stakes","paragraph":"“You win some and lose some, and we get beaten loads of times in good races, but you have to compete. That's what it's all about.","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/sport\/cricket\/uae-cricketers-amir-hayat-and-ashfaq-ahmed-charged-under-icc-anti-corruption-code-1.1077020","title":"UAE cricketers Amir Hayat and Ashfaq Ahmed charged under ICC anti-corruption code","paragraph":"Mohammed Naveed, the former UAE captain, batsman Shaiman Anwar, and fast bowler Qadeer Ahmed, are awaiting judgement on numerous charges of breaching the anti-corruption code.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Mohammed Naveed","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"UAE","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Shaiman Anwar","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Qadeer Ahmed","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/the-americas\/coronavirus-heart-damage-detected-in-infected-young-athletes-1.1076374","title":"Coronavirus: heart damage detected in infected young athletes","paragraph":"US study indicates that even asymptomatic cases could suffer cardiac impairment ","entity":[{"entity_text":"US","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/government\/dubai-s-expo-follows-a-legacy-that-includes-the-eiffel-tower-and-disney-s-small-world-1.1076421","title":"Dubai's Expo follows a legacy that includes the Eiffel Tower and Disney's Small World","paragraph":"“Maybe you don't think of Moldova every day, but Moldova had its own separate pavilion in Milan 2015 and made a big splash, as did Angola,” said Mr Chappell.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Moldova","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"every day","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Moldova","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Milan","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"2015","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Angola","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Mr Chappell","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/technology\/elon-musk-accuses-bill-gates-of-having-no-clue-about-batteries-1.1076774","title":"Elon Musk accuses Bill Gates of having 'no clue' about batteries","paragraph":"H:40 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:40 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/europe\/design-guru-sir-terence-conran-for-whom-the-word-lifestyle-was-created-dies-1.1076570","title":"Design guru Sir Terence Conran, for whom the word lifestyle was created, dies","paragraph":"H:40 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:40 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/other-sport\/team-emirates-tadej-pogacar-moves-into-second-in-tour-de-france-1.1076312","title":"Team Emirates' Tadej Pogacar moves into second in Tour de France","paragraph":"Caleb Ewan claims second victory in Tour de France","entity":[{"entity_text":"second","entity_type":"ORDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Tour de France","entity_type":"EVENT"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/smoke-from-thursday-s-beirut-port-fire-no-danger-to-city-1.1076929","title":"Smoke from Thursday's Beirut port fire 'no danger to city'","paragraph":"H:42 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:42 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/government\/abu-dhabi-launches-landmark-strategy-for-people-of-determination-1.1076508","title":"Abu Dhabi launches landmark strategy for 'People of Determination'","paragraph":"“Today’s launch of the comprehensive strategy for People of Determination reaffirms our commitment to inclusion, equality and empowerment for all members of UAE society, upholding everyone’s right to participate fully and with dignity in our community,&quot; said Sheikh Mohamed. ","entity":[{"entity_text":"People of Determination","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"UAE","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Sheikh Mohamed","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/environment\/working-from-home-could-create-surge-in-gulf-s-ac-bills-and-emissions-1.1077001","title":"Working from home could create surge in Gulf's AC bills and emissions","paragraph":"“If you’re in a hot climate, and you’re adjusted to that hot climate, you can go higher,” he said.","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/uae\/government\/uae-s-updated-list-of-fines-for-covid-19-rule-breakers-1.1076832","title":"UAE's updated list of fines for Covid-19 rule breakers","paragraph":"The daily number is the highest recorded since the pandemic broke out and officials in recent days have again warned that the rise in cases is down to the lax attitude of individuals and institutions who failed to abide by regulations.","entity":[{"entity_text":"daily","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"recent days","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/al-hilal-report-six-positive-coronavirus-cases-in-lead-up-to-asian-champions-league-restart-1.1076946","title":"Al Hilal report six positive coronavirus cases in lead-up to Asian Champions League restart","paragraph":"AFC reported that five players and one member of management from the reigning champions had tested positive, alongside a player from host team Al Duhail","entity":[{"entity_text":"AFC","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"five","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"one","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Al Duhail","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/in-beirut-a-rescued-pelican-becomes-symbol-of-hope-in-crisis-stricken-lebanon-1.1077035","title":"In Beirut, a rescued pelican becomes symbol of hope in crisis-stricken Lebanon","paragraph":"Three times a day a large white pelican waddles up to a seaside restaurant on Beirut’s corniche for a snack of fresh fish, its wellbeing closely guarded by locals and the fishermen who found him dying in the open sea last February.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Three","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Beirut","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"last February","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/arts-culture\/music\/rolling-stones-set-record-for-topping-charts-across-six-different-decades-1.1076425","title":"Rolling Stones set record for topping charts across six different decades","paragraph":"H:38 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:38 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/the-middle-east-framed-regional-photography-for-september-12-2020-1.1076585","title":"The Middle East Framed - regional photography for September 12, 2020","paragraph":"L:28 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:28 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/cricket\/ipl-2020-letting-schoolboy-prodigy-tom-banton-go-was-the-biggest-decision-for-dougie-brown-1.1076568","title":"IPL 2020: Letting schoolboy prodigy Tom Banton go was the 'biggest decision' for Dougie Brown","paragraph":"“We had to get special dispensation from the league, because at that stage we weren’t allowed to play 13-year olds as it was considered to be too dangerous,” Brown said.","entity":[{"entity_text":"13-year","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Brown","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/asia\/afghan-government-calls-for-ceasefire-as-historic-peace-talks-with-taliban-begin-1.1076423","title":"Afghan government calls for ceasefire as historic peace talks with Taliban begin","paragraph":"L:25 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:25 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/cricket\/ipl-2020-team-profiles-delhi-capitals-key-players-fixtures-and-predictions-1.1076848","title":"IPL 2020 team profiles: Delhi Capitals' key players, fixtures and predictions","paragraph":"Captain: Shreyas Iyer. In six seasons before last year, Delhi did not get any higher than third last in the IPL league table. With inexperienced Iyer at the helm, though, they thrived. He will have an understanding of UAE grounds, too. He was part of the India side that played at the Under 19 World Cup here in 2014.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Shreyas Iyer","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"six seasons before last year","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Delhi","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"third","entity_type":"ORDINAL"},{"entity_text":"IPL","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Iyer","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"UAE grounds","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"India","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"World Cup","entity_type":"EVENT"},{"entity_text":"2014","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/health\/coronavirus-covid-19-cases-rise-again-as-931-new-infections-are-recorded-1.1076190","title":"Coronavirus: Covid-19 cases rise again as 931 new infections are recorded","paragraph":"UAE reports 930 new cases, the highest in four months","entity":[{"entity_text":"UAE","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"930","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"four months","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/cricket\/ipl-2020-team-profiles-delhi-capitals-key-players-fixtures-and-predictions-1.1076848","title":"IPL 2020 team profiles: Delhi Capitals' key players, fixtures and predictions","paragraph":"Coach: Ricky Ponting","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/world\/world-in-focus-best-photos-for-september-11-2020-1.1076256","title":"World in focus - best photos for September 11, 2020","paragraph":"H:37 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:37 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/opinion\/comment\/my-son-and-i-were-lucky-to-access-the-best-of-us-health-care-1.1076517","title":"My son and I were lucky to access the best of US health care","paragraph":"Most people in the US have either private insurance or a combination of various state or federal programmes. But often these programmes don’t provide access to the best facilities. There is not much choice if you are poor: you take what you can get, which is why many poor people don’t go to the doctor.","entity":[{"entity_text":"US","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/education\/coronavirus-affordable-dubai-schools-find-creative-ways-to-open-amid-covid-19-1.1076387","title":"Coronavirus: Affordable Dubai schools find creative ways to open amid Covid-19","paragraph":"The school created awareness videos and informed parents through online groups.","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/world\/asia\/afghan-government-negotiators-leave-for-peace-talks-with-taliban-1.1076216","title":"Afghan government negotiators leave for peace talks with Taliban","paragraph":"&quot;We are going to Doha to tell the Taliban that you cannot succeed by force,&quot; Abdul Hafiz Mansour, a member of Kabul's delegation, told reporters at the capital's airport.","entity":[{"entity_text":"&quot;We","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Doha","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Taliban","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Abdul Hafiz Mansour","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Kabul","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/europe\/uk-signs-japan-trade-deal-amid-furious-brexit-wrangling-1.1076222","title":"UK signs Japan trade deal amid furious Brexit wrangling","paragraph":" Striking an accord with the world’s third-largest economy has been a priority for Johnson, who is eager to demonstrate the ability to sign trade deals as an independent country — a key plank of the Brexit campaign he led. The UK benefited from the EU-Japan free trade agreement and needed a deal to avoid tariffs on commerce with Japan at the end of the year.","entity":[{"entity_text":"third","entity_type":"ORDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Johnson","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Brexit","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"UK","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"EU","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Japan","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Japan","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"the end of the year","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/markets\/saudi-arabia-s-bindawood-grocery-retailer-to-raise-as-much-as-585m-from-ipo-1.1076860","title":"Saudi Arabia's BinDawood grocery retailer to raise as much as $585m from IPO","paragraph":"L:28 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:28 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/al-hilal-report-six-positive-coronavirus-cases-in-lead-up-to-asian-champions-league-restart-1.1076946","title":"Al Hilal report six positive coronavirus cases in lead-up to Asian Champions League restart","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/business\/generation-start-up-ikcon-cooks-up-plans-to-take-bigger-bite-out-of-food-delivery-market-1.1076539","title":"Generation Start-up: iKcon cooks up plans to take bigger bite out of food delivery market","paragraph":"Name: iKcon","entity":[{"entity_text":"iKcon","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/government\/dubai-s-expo-follows-a-legacy-that-includes-the-eiffel-tower-and-disney-s-small-world-1.1076421","title":"Dubai's Expo follows a legacy that includes the Eiffel Tower and Disney's Small World","paragraph":"“People can experience cultures they're not necessarily as familiar with and lots of interesting things can happen,” he said in an interview from his home in San Francisco.”","entity":[{"entity_text":"San Francisco","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/volkswagen-s-truckmaking-unit-to-cut-9-500-jobs-1.1076202","title":"Volkswagen&rsquo;s truckmaking unit to cut 9,500 jobs","paragraph":"H:40 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:40 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/government\/dubai-issues-hundreds-of-fines-at-malls-in-campaign-against-covid-19-offenders-1.1076903","title":"Dubai issues hundreds of fines at malls in campaign against Covid-19 offenders","paragraph":"Last week, the authorities in Dubai closed a Day-to-Day outlet for holding a flash sale that drew large crowds. Footage showed shoppers spilling out on to the street, breaching social distancing guidelines at the discount chain. It was fined Dh50,000.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Last week","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Dubai","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/hamas-loses-appeal-against-eu-terror-listing-1.1076315","title":"Hamas loses appeal against EU terror listing","paragraph":" The EU’s General Court has rejected previous attempts by the militant group to recover its assets in Europe after a series of decisions by the European Council in 2010, 2014 and 2017.","entity":[{"entity_text":"EU","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"General Court","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Europe","entity_type":"LOC"},{"entity_text":"the European Council","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"2010","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"2014","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"2017","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/government\/abu-dhabi-launches-landmark-strategy-for-people-of-determination-1.1076508","title":"Abu Dhabi launches landmark strategy for 'People of Determination'","paragraph":"Sheikh Mohamed bin Zayed, Crown Prince of Abu Dhabi and Deputy Supreme Commander of the Armed Forces, launched the strategy on Saturday. ","entity":[{"entity_text":"Mohamed bin Zayed","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Crown Prince","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Abu Dhabi","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"the Armed Forces","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Saturday","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/in-beirut-a-rescued-pelican-becomes-symbol-of-hope-in-crisis-stricken-lebanon-1.1077035","title":"In Beirut, a rescued pelican becomes symbol of hope in crisis-stricken Lebanon","paragraph":"At least 190 people died as a result of the blast and local authorities said that the chemicals had been stored unsafely for seven years. On Thursday, a little more than a month later, a massive fire erupted at the port stoking fears that hazardous materials are still being stored without proper security measures, with more explosives later discovered stored there.","entity":[{"entity_text":"At least 190","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"seven years","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Thursday","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"a little more than a month later","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/education\/mbzuai-signs-first-higher-education-co-operation-plan-between-uae-and-israel-1.1076958","title":"MBZUAI signs first higher education co-operation plan between UAE and Israel","paragraph":"The company will use its new office to focus on areas including Covid-19 diagnostic solutions, smart cities, renewable energies and water supply solutions. ","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/lebanese-soldiers-fire-live-bullets-as-protesters-march-on-presidential-palace-1.1076709","title":"Lebanese soldiers fire live bullets as protesters march on presidential palace","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/world\/the-americas\/nicolas-maduro-says-us-spy-captured-near-venezuelan-refineries-1.1076472","title":"Nicolas Maduro says US spy captured near Venezuelan refineries","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/lifestyle\/comment\/as-a-mum-here-are-three-reasons-i-d-never-have-a-gender-reveal-party-1.1077017","title":"As a mum, here are three reasons I'd never have a gender reveal party ...","paragraph":"H:37 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:37 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/education\/mbzuai-signs-first-higher-education-co-operation-plan-between-uae-and-israel-1.1076958","title":"MBZUAI signs first higher education co-operation plan between UAE and Israel","paragraph":"H:38 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:38 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/horse-racing\/magical-gets-the-better-of-ghaiyyath-in-irish-champion-stakes-1.1076850","title":"Magical gets the better of Ghaiyyath in Irish Champion Stakes","paragraph":"“You can't expect to win everyday, but when your turns comes you're delighted. Ghaiyyath is a great horse and it was great he came.","entity":[{"entity_text":"everyday","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/opinion\/comment\/uae-and-mexico-will-overcome-distance-to-come-closer-1.1075841","title":"UAE and Mexico will overcome distance to come closer","paragraph":"Graciela Marquez, Mexico Minister of Economy: Ties make even more sense in today's world","entity":[{"entity_text":"Graciela Marquez","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Mexico","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"today","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/lifestyle\/travel\/indian-airlines-face-two-week-suspensions-for-unruly-passenger-behaviour-1.1076573","title":"Indian airlines face two week suspensions for unruly passenger behaviour","paragraph":"A video shared on social media and shot by a passenger on the same flight shows reporters crowding around the actor. Many of the passengers involved also failed to wear face masks properly.","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/sport\/cricket\/ipl-2020-letting-schoolboy-prodigy-tom-banton-go-was-the-biggest-decision-for-dougie-brown-1.1076568","title":"IPL 2020: Letting schoolboy prodigy Tom Banton go was the 'biggest decision' for Dougie Brown","paragraph":"He was a schoolboy prodigy, a phenomenal player","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/sorry-alex-jurgen-klopp-apologises-to-ferguson-for-4am-text-after-liverpool-s-title-win-1.1076404","title":"'Sorry, Alex!' Jurgen Klopp apologises to Ferguson for 4am text after Liverpool's title win","paragraph":"H:38 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:38 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/harry-maguire-to-remain-manchester-united-captain-despite-court-case-1.1076519","title":"Harry Maguire to remain Manchester United captain despite court case","paragraph":"Solskjaer said Maguire had coped well with the incident in Greece.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Solskjaer","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Maguire","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Greece","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/asia\/india-reports-record-daily-jump-in-covid-cases-for-second-straight-day-1.1076521","title":"India reports record daily jump in Covid cases for second straight day","paragraph":"But the growth in infections in India is faster than anywhere else in the world, as cases surge through urban and rural areas.","entity":[{"entity_text":"India","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/world-in-focus-best-photos-for-september-12-2020-1.1076536","title":"World in focus - best photos for September 12, 2020","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/callum-wilson-8-jeff-hendrick-8-mark-noble-5-west-ham-v-newcastle-player-ratings-1.1076831","title":"Callum Wilson 8, Jeff Hendrick 8; Mark Noble 5: West Ham v Newcastle player ratings","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/sport\/f1\/lewis-hamilton-storms-to-tuscan-grand-prix-pole-position-1.1076672","title":"Lewis Hamilton storms to Tuscan Grand Prix pole position","paragraph":"L:28 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:28 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/opinion\/comment\/my-son-and-i-were-lucky-to-access-the-best-of-us-health-care-1.1076517","title":"My son and I were lucky to access the best of US health care","paragraph":"But the Lenox Hill ER was a far cry from the spotless corridors of the hospital for special surgery. Waiting for my son to emerge from his five-hour-long procedure, I sat in plush chairs with plenty of ports to plug in my computer and iPhone. A TV blasted CNN. There was a spiritual centre (for Muslims, Christians, Jews) and a Starbucks nearby.","entity":[{"entity_text":"five-hour","entity_type":"TIME"},{"entity_text":"iPhone","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"CNN","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Muslims","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"Christians","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"Jews","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"Starbucks","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/lifestyle\/food\/tributes-paid-to-founder-of-gerard-cafe-after-news-of-his-death-1.1076439","title":"Tributes paid to founder of Gerard Cafe after news of his death","paragraph":"“In our remembrance of a legend in Dubai. Our great Gerard who touched so many hearts. We already miss you. Love you papa,” posts on Facebook and Instagram read.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Dubai","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Facebook","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Instagram","entity_type":"PRODUCT"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/beirut-port-fire-private-firms-say-lax-oversight-led-to-blaze-1.1076308","title":"Beirut port fire: private firms say lax oversight led to blaze","paragraph":"“Let’s say we wanted to hire engineers to rebuild and assess damages after the explosion, we would have had to submit a list of names with phone numbers and addresses of what they do and get the authorisation from the military police,” he said.","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/business\/money\/covid-19-accelerates-urgency-of-people-wanting-to-retire-in-secure-countries-1.1076628","title":"Covid-19 accelerates urgency of people wanting to retire in secure countries","paragraph":"“However, retirees can continue to benefit from the tax-free status of Dubai residency, in terms of income and investments, where they may have suffered tax when drawing their retirement income in their home country.”","entity":[{"entity_text":"Dubai","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/sorry-alex-jurgen-klopp-apologises-to-ferguson-for-4am-text-after-liverpool-s-title-win-1.1076404","title":"'Sorry, Alex!' Jurgen Klopp apologises to Ferguson for 4am text after Liverpool's title win","paragraph":"Ferguson sent a congratulatory message to Liverpool manager Klopp after the Reds ended their 30-year wait to be crowned English champions following Manchester City's defeat at Chelsea in June.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Ferguson","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Liverpool","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Reds","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"30-year","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"English","entity_type":"LANGUAGE"},{"entity_text":"Manchester City's","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Chelsea","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"June","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/arts-culture\/film\/venice-film-festival-gears-up-to-award-masked-golden-lion-winner-1.1076506","title":"Venice Film Festival gears up to award masked Golden Lion winner","paragraph":"Many directors saluted the festival's organisers for going ahead with the event.","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/business\/money\/can-my-employer-pay-my-gratuity-in-instalments-1.1076393","title":"&lsquo;Can my employer pay my gratuity in instalments?&rsquo;","paragraph":"H:37 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:37 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/pierre-emerick-aubameyang-on-target-as-arsenal-hammer-fulham-in-premier-league-season-opener-1.1076601","title":"Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang on target as Arsenal hammer Fulham in Premier League season opener","paragraph":"Arsenal's passion was in evidence before the kick-off when Eddie Nketiah and Dani Ceballos clashed in the warm-up, a late challenge led to the two squaring up and needing to be separated.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Arsenal","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Eddie Nketiah","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Dani Ceballos","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"two","entity_type":"CARDINAL"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/f1\/lewis-hamilton-storms-to-tuscan-grand-prix-pole-position-1.1076672","title":"Lewis Hamilton storms to Tuscan Grand Prix pole position","paragraph":"But Hamilton saved his best for the main show, edging out Valtteri Bottas by 0.059 seconds as Mercedes secured another front-row lockout.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Hamilton","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Valtteri Bottas","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0.059 seconds","entity_type":"TIME"},{"entity_text":"Mercedes","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/in-beirut-a-rescued-pelican-becomes-symbol-of-hope-in-crisis-stricken-lebanon-1.1077035","title":"In Beirut, a rescued pelican becomes symbol of hope in crisis-stricken Lebanon","paragraph":"L:25 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:25 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/prada-s-sales-in-china-recover-strongly-as-shops-reopen-1.1076268","title":"Prada's sales in China recover strongly as shops reopen","paragraph":"H:37 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:37 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/arts-culture\/film\/the-man-who-sold-his-skin-how-a-back-tattoo-inspired-tunisian-director-kaouther-ben-hania-s-latest-film-1.1076262","title":"'The Man Who Sold His Skin': How a back tattoo inspired Tunisian director Kaouther Ben Hania's latest film","paragraph":"The film re-examines the portrait of the artist through the story of a Syrian refugee","entity":[{"entity_text":"Syrian","entity_type":"NORP"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/money\/can-my-employer-pay-my-gratuity-in-instalments-1.1076393","title":"&lsquo;Can my employer pay my gratuity in instalments?&rsquo;","paragraph":"It appears that this employer has breached multiple articles of the UAE Labour Law and HK has strong grounds to bring a case against them. He can seek further advice from the Ministry of Human Resources and Emiratisation via their call centre (800 60) or through its online chat function at www.mohre.gov.ae.","entity":[{"entity_text":"the UAE Labour Law","entity_type":"LAW"},{"entity_text":"HK","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"the Ministry of Human Resources and Emiratisation","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/lifestyle\/wellbeing\/the-27-year-old-vet-going-viral-on-tiktok-1.1076914","title":"The 27-year-old vet going viral on TikTok","paragraph":"The 27-year-old currently has more than 985,000 followers on the platform and says he will continue doing videos specifically for pet owners as long as they find it useful. ","entity":[{"entity_text":"27-year-old","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"more than 985,000","entity_type":"CARDINAL"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/money\/covid-19-accelerates-urgency-of-people-wanting-to-retire-in-secure-countries-1.1076628","title":"Covid-19 accelerates urgency of people wanting to retire in secure countries","paragraph":"There are many avenues for expatriates to generate comfortable levels of retirement income, says Mr Ritchie. The most common ones include pensions, investment funds, annuities and cash savings.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Mr Ritchie","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/opinion\/comment\/why-iran-is-bent-on-escalating-tensions-in-the-gulf-1.1076557","title":"Why Iran is bent on escalating tensions in the Gulf","paragraph":"It might make sense to assume, therefore, that Beijing would be hoping to see Mr Trump defeated in November. But that is an inaccurate assessment to make, because there now exists a bipartisan consensus in Washington over the need for the US to contain China's rise. America has demonstrated that when its national interests are at stake, plans are made not over four years but four decades.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Beijing","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Mr Trump","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"November","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Washington","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"US","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"China","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"America","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"four years","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"four decades","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/health\/coronavirus-workers-find-comfort-in-prayer-as-churches-reopen-in-industrial-areas-1.1076372","title":"Coronavirus: Workers find comfort in prayer as churches reopen in industrial areas","paragraph":"St Paul’s Church began services on Monday evening in Mussaffah, a densely populated industrial area of the capital, after months of closure due to the Covid-19 pandemic.","entity":[{"entity_text":"St Paul’s Church","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Monday evening","entity_type":"TIME"},{"entity_text":"Mussaffah","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"months","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/government\/uae-assists-iraq-argentina-and-paraguay-with-covid-19-relief-1.1076473","title":"UAE assists Iraq, Argentina and Paraguay with Covid-19 relief","paragraph":"In the Americas, the UAE has previously sent protective gear to Columbia, 500,000 Covid-19 testing kits to Brazil and financial support to US charities and organisations that provide food to those in need.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Americas","entity_type":"LOC"},{"entity_text":"UAE","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Columbia","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"500,000","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Brazil","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"US","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/cricket\/ipl-2020-team-profiles-chennai-super-kings-key-players-fixtures-and-predictions-1.1076345","title":"IPL 2020 team profiles: Chennai Super Kings key players, fixtures and predictions","paragraph":"Captain: MS Dhoni. The next couple of months were due to be the great captain’s international swansong. Then the T20 World Cup was postponed, and he said goodbye in absentia instead. It will be interesting to see what impact the Covid-enforced break from cricket will have had on his ageing limbs.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Dhoni","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"The next couple of months","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"the T20 World Cup","entity_type":"EVENT"},{"entity_text":"Covid","entity_type":"NORP"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/world-in-focus-best-photos-for-september-12-2020-1.1076536","title":"World in focus - best photos for September 12, 2020","paragraph":"Take a look at some of the best images from around the world in the past 24 hours","entity":[{"entity_text":"the past 24 hours","entity_type":"TIME"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/government\/dubai-s-24-hour-hotline-gives-elderly-secure-line-to-request-help-or-report-abuse-1.1077037","title":"Dubai's 24-hour hotline gives elderly secure line to request help or report abuse","paragraph":"Requests for information and complaints can also be reported to: Seniorprotection@cda.gov.ae or by calling the main call centre at 8002121.","entity":[{"entity_text":"8002121","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/cricket\/ipl-2020-letting-schoolboy-prodigy-tom-banton-go-was-the-biggest-decision-for-dougie-brown-1.1076568","title":"IPL 2020: Letting schoolboy prodigy Tom Banton go was the 'biggest decision' for Dougie Brown","paragraph":"All of which jars – on the surface at least – with what happened subsequently.","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/business\/money\/covid-19-accelerates-urgency-of-people-wanting-to-retire-in-secure-countries-1.1076628","title":"Covid-19 accelerates urgency of people wanting to retire in secure countries","paragraph":"If you have more than a few years before retirement, then investing sensibly in stock and bond funds is the fastest way to grow your money over the long term without taking excessive risk on investments, says Steve Cronin, founder of DeadSimpleSaving.com.","entity":[{"entity_text":"more than a few years","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Steve Cronin","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"DeadSimpleSaving.com","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/the-americas\/trump-s-miracle-covid-drug-spurned-by-us-hospitals-1.1076328","title":"Trump's miracle Covid drug spurned by US hospitals","paragraph":"L:28 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:28 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/arts-culture\/film\/the-dinner-saudi-and-emirati-trio-unite-to-create-female-led-film-and-hope-others-follows-in-their-footsteps-1.1076274","title":"'The Dinner': Saudi and Emirati trio unite to create female-led film &ndash; and hope others follows in their footsteps","paragraph":"H:41 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:41 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/dramatic-rise-in-coronavirus-cases-among-youngsters-in-england-1.1076207","title":"Dramatic rise in coronavirus cases among youngsters in England","paragraph":"During the most recent week, the ONS estimates that there were around 0.58 new Covid-19 infections for every 10,000 people per day in England, equating to approximately 3,200 new cases per day.","entity":[{"entity_text":"the most recent week","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"ONS","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"10,000","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"England","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"approximately 3,200","entity_type":"CARDINAL"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/prada-s-sales-in-china-recover-strongly-as-shops-reopen-1.1076268","title":"Prada's sales in China recover strongly as shops reopen","paragraph":"The virus first emerged in China late last year and then spread to the rest of the world, forcing high-end retailers to temporarily close stores and idle manufacturing sites.","entity":[{"entity_text":"first","entity_type":"ORDINAL"},{"entity_text":"China","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"late last year","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/cricket\/ipl-2020-rajasthan-royals-refine-moneyball-philosophy-to-remain-at-cutting-edge-of-innovation-1.1076942","title":"IPL 2020: Rajasthan Royals refine 'Moneyball' philosophy to remain at cutting edge of innovation","paragraph":"Chairman Ranjit Barthakur and COO Jake Lush McCrum reveal why they are known as the 'smart' team","entity":[{"entity_text":"Ranjit Barthakur","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/arts-culture\/film\/the-man-who-sold-his-skin-how-a-back-tattoo-inspired-tunisian-director-kaouther-ben-hania-s-latest-film-1.1076262","title":"'The Man Who Sold His Skin': How a back tattoo inspired Tunisian director Kaouther Ben Hania's latest film","paragraph":"L:25 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:25 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/europe\/uk-finally-launches-a-coronavirus-tracking-app-1.1076258","title":"UK finally launches a coronavirus tracking app","paragraph":"The government’s first attempt to build a home-grown app ended in failure.","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/world\/africa\/liberia-declares-rape-a-national-emergency-1.1076603","title":"Liberia declares rape a national emergency","paragraph":"Incidents of rape appear to have risen sharply this year, however.","entity":[{"entity_text":"this year","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/european-powers-push-iran-hard-to-comply-with-nuclear-deal-1.1076214","title":"European powers push Iran hard to comply with nuclear deal","paragraph":"L:28 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:28 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/egypt-discovers-13-mummies-believed-to-be-2-500-years-old-1.1076859","title":"Egypt discovers 13 mummies believed to be 2,500 years old","paragraph":"H:41 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:41 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/other-sport\/team-emirates-tadej-pogacar-moves-into-second-in-tour-de-france-1.1076312","title":"Team Emirates' Tadej Pogacar moves into second in Tour de France","paragraph":"11. Daniel Martin, Ireland, Israel Start-Up Nation, 4:31.","entity":[{"entity_text":"11","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Daniel Martin","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Ireland","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Israel Start-Up Nation","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"4:31","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/arts-culture\/art\/why-lebanese-artist-chafa-ghaddar-is-focused-on-frescoes-they-give-me-goosebumps-1.1075914","title":"Why Lebanese artist Chafa Ghaddar is focused on frescoes: 'They give me goosebumps'","paragraph":"How one 14-year-old is helping her younger brother travel the world through chalk","entity":[{"entity_text":"one","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"14-year-old","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/lionel-messi-makes-first-barcelona-appearance-since-transfer-u-turn-in-pictures-1.1076801","title":"Lionel Messi makes first Barcelona appearance since transfer u-turn - in pictures","paragraph":"H:38 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:38 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/lifestyle\/travel\/etihad-resumes-flights-to-morocco-as-the-country-welcomes-travellers-1.1076470","title":"Etihad resumes flights to Morocco as the country welcomes travellers","paragraph":"The Abu Dhabi airline will fly to Casablanca from September 19 and to Rabat by October 28","entity":[{"entity_text":"Abu Dhabi","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Casablanca","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"September 19","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Rabat","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"October 28","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/economy\/swedish-regulator-worries-about-lack-of-physical-cash-1.1076493","title":"Swedish regulator worries about lack of physical cash","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/sport\/cricket\/uae-cricketers-amir-hayat-and-ashfaq-ahmed-charged-under-icc-anti-corruption-code-1.1077020","title":"UAE cricketers Amir Hayat and Ashfaq Ahmed charged under ICC anti-corruption code","paragraph":"“Failing to disclose to the ACU [without unnecessary delay] full details of any approaches or invitations received by the participant to engage in corrupt conduct under the Anti-Corruption Code.","entity":[{"entity_text":"ACU","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"the Anti-Corruption Code","entity_type":"LAW"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/markets\/saudi-arabia-s-bindawood-grocery-retailer-to-raise-as-much-as-585m-from-ipo-1.1076860","title":"Saudi Arabia's BinDawood grocery retailer to raise as much as $585m from IPO","paragraph":"Initially, all the offered shares will be provisionally allocated to institutional investors but may be later reduced to 90 per cent, depending on demand by individual investors, the company said.","entity":[{"entity_text":"90 per cent","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/uk-awards-burberry-1-8m-in-coronavirus-contracts-1.1076196","title":"UK awards Burberry &pound;1.8m in coronavirus contracts","paragraph":"Ministers have suspended the UK’s standard fair competition rules to enable contracts to be issued “with extreme urgency”.","entity":[{"entity_text":"UK","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/opinion\/comment\/is-erdogan-interested-in-a-deal-with-europe-1.1076466","title":"Is Erdogan interested in a deal with Europe?","paragraph":"The Greek Prime Minister Kyriakos Mitsotakis has called for the Europeans to adopt a quick, sharp shock strategy when it puts together its sanctions measures. Turkey’s complaint is that it is being shut out of the hydro-carbon riches of the sea – huge natural gas basins have been discovered in recent decades – and that its coastline is unfairly hemmed in by Greek waters.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Greek","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"Kyriakos Mitsotakis","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Europeans","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"Turkey","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"recent decades","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Greek","entity_type":"NORP"}]}
{"href":"\/arts-culture\/art\/why-lebanese-artist-chafa-ghaddar-is-focused-on-frescoes-they-give-me-goosebumps-1.1075914","title":"Why Lebanese artist Chafa Ghaddar is focused on frescoes: 'They give me goosebumps'","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/uae\/science\/rockets-are-hard-elon-musk-offers-sympathy-after-astra-s-spacecraft-crash-lands-in-alaska-1.1076938","title":"'Rockets are hard': Elon Musk offers sympathy after Astra's spacecraft crash lands in Alaska","paragraph":"On Saturday, a Chinese rocket also experienced a failed launch attempt after facing an anomaly.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Saturday","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Chinese","entity_type":"NORP"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/government\/abu-dhabi-launches-landmark-strategy-for-people-of-determination-1.1076508","title":"Abu Dhabi launches landmark strategy for 'People of Determination'","paragraph":"H:37 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:37 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/tennis\/dominic-thiem-to-face-alexander-zverev-in-final-as-us-open-prepares-to-crown-a-first-time-grand-slam-champion-1.1076396","title":"Dominic Thiem to face Alexander Zverev in final as US Open prepares to crown a first-time Grand Slam champion","paragraph":"The 27-year-old Thiem won 6-2, 7-6, 7-6 in two hours and 56 minutes inside Arthur Ashe Stadium to reach his fourth Grand Slam final.","entity":[{"entity_text":"27-year-old","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Thiem","entity_type":"WORK_OF_ART"},{"entity_text":"6","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"7","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"7","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"two hours and 56 minutes","entity_type":"TIME"},{"entity_text":"Arthur Ashe Stadium","entity_type":"FAC"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/prada-s-sales-in-china-recover-strongly-as-shops-reopen-1.1076268","title":"Prada's sales in China recover strongly as shops reopen","paragraph":"The industry's overall sales are expected to decline by up to 35 per cent in 2020, but luxury groups are betting on a strong rebound in mainland China to limit the damage.","entity":[{"entity_text":"up to","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"2020","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"China","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/generation-start-up-ikcon-cooks-up-plans-to-take-bigger-bite-out-of-food-delivery-market-1.1076539","title":"Generation Start-up: iKcon cooks up plans to take bigger bite out of food delivery market","paragraph":"The concept has been gaining traction. Uber founder Travis Kalanick acquired US-based CloudKitchens in 2018 and has been buying competitors such as Foodstars, which is based in London, to grow the business.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Travis Kalanick","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"US","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"CloudKitchens","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"2018","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Foodstars","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"London","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/government\/dubai-police-arrests-man-for-breaking-quarantine-and-bragging-about-it-1.1076697","title":"Dubai Police arrests man for breaking quarantine and bragging about it","paragraph":"___________","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/un-steps-up-covid-19-measures-at-syrian-refugee-camps-in-jordan-1.1076778","title":"UN steps up COVID-19 measures at Syrian refugee camps in Jordan","paragraph":"H:37 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:37 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/europe\/russia-local-elections-gauge-ruling-party-s-power-1.1076852","title":"Russia local elections gauge ruling party's power","paragraph":"H:37 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:37 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/economy\/swedish-regulator-worries-about-lack-of-physical-cash-1.1076493","title":"Swedish regulator worries about lack of physical cash","paragraph":"But Scandinavia’s next generation may not know what a real piggy bank is, consigning the once-ubiquitous savings vessel popularised by storyteller Hans Christian Andersen to the history books, alongside rotary phones and floppy disks.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Scandinavia","entity_type":"LOC"},{"entity_text":"Hans Christian Andersen","entity_type":"NORP"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/health\/coronavirus-workers-find-comfort-in-prayer-as-churches-reopen-in-industrial-areas-1.1076372","title":"Coronavirus: Workers find comfort in prayer as churches reopen in industrial areas","paragraph":"H:38 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:38 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/the-americas\/us-gears-for-rising-death-toll-in-west-coast-wildfires-1.1076707","title":"US gears for rising death toll in West Coast wildfires","paragraph":"Ten people have been confirmed dead from that blaze in Butte County, which was driven at unprecedented pace toward the city of Oroville earlier in the week by strong, dry winds and soaring temperatures.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Ten","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Butte County","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Oroville","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"the week","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/aviation\/thai-airways-awaits-court-ruling-on-its-debt-restructuring-plans-1.1076897","title":"Thai Airways awaits court ruling on its debt restructuring plans","paragraph":"L:28 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:28 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/in-beirut-a-rescued-pelican-becomes-symbol-of-hope-in-crisis-stricken-lebanon-1.1077035","title":"In Beirut, a rescued pelican becomes symbol of hope in crisis-stricken Lebanon","paragraph":" “Lebanon is the second most important route of bird migration in the world, and one of the worst countries for hunting, along with Italy, Egypt, and Syria,” said Ms Youssef.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Lebanon","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"second","entity_type":"ORDINAL"},{"entity_text":"one","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Italy","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Egypt","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Syria","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Ms Youssef","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/other-sport\/world-s-most-expensive-stadium-with-largest-videoboard-unveiled-in-los-angeles-in-pictures-1.1076362","title":"World's most expensive stadium with largest videoboard unveiled in Los Angeles - in pictures","paragraph":"H:42 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:42 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/lifestyle\/comment\/as-a-mum-here-are-three-reasons-i-d-never-have-a-gender-reveal-party-1.1077017","title":"As a mum, here are three reasons I'd never have a gender reveal party ...","paragraph":"In the performative age of social media, it can feel like everything, no matter how personal, has to be over-the-top, planned, photographed and caught on tape. If there isn't a photo of him on one knee, did he really propose?","entity":[{"entity_text":"one","entity_type":"CARDINAL"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/un-steps-up-covid-19-measures-at-syrian-refugee-camps-in-jordan-1.1076778","title":"UN steps up COVID-19 measures at Syrian refugee camps in Jordan","paragraph":"The UN refugee agency is stepping up efforts to curb the spread of Covid-19 among tens of thousands of Syrians in camps in Jordan after the first cases were confirmed last week, the head of the agency in the country said on Saturday.","entity":[{"entity_text":"UN","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"tens of thousands","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Syrians","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"Jordan","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"first","entity_type":"ORDINAL"},{"entity_text":"last week","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Saturday","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/europe\/tear-gas-fired-on-migrant-protesters-demanding-resettlement-1.1076495","title":"Tear gas fired on migrant protesters demanding resettlement","paragraph":"Islanders protest over overcrowded refugee camps","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/in-beirut-a-rescued-pelican-becomes-symbol-of-hope-in-crisis-stricken-lebanon-1.1077035","title":"In Beirut, a rescued pelican becomes symbol of hope in crisis-stricken Lebanon","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/sport\/other-sport\/world-s-most-expensive-stadium-with-largest-videoboard-unveiled-in-los-angeles-in-pictures-1.1076362","title":"World's most expensive stadium with largest videoboard unveiled in Los Angeles - in pictures","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/business\/technology\/how-internet-searches-for-stomach-symptoms-helped-predict-covid-19-hot-spots-1.1076781","title":"How internet searches for stomach symptoms helped predict Covid-19 hot spots","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/harry-maguire-to-remain-manchester-united-captain-despite-court-case-1.1076519","title":"Harry Maguire to remain Manchester United captain despite court case","paragraph":"H:41 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:41 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/asia\/afghan-government-negotiators-leave-for-peace-talks-with-taliban-1.1076216","title":"Afghan government negotiators leave for peace talks with Taliban","paragraph":"L:27 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:27 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/dramatic-rise-in-coronavirus-cases-among-youngsters-in-england-1.1076207","title":"Dramatic rise in coronavirus cases among youngsters in England","paragraph":"Health Secretary Matt Hancock has described it as a “defining moment”, saying it would help to contain the virus “at a critical time”.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Health","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Matt Hancock","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/arts-culture\/art\/abu-dhabi-arts-centre-warehouse421-reopens-2021-will-be-year-of-experimentation-1.1076968","title":"Abu Dhabi arts centre Warehouse421 reopens: '2021 will be year of experimentation'","paragraph":"L:25 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:25 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/afghan-taliban-peace-talks-start-in-shadow-of-twin-towers-anniversary-1.1076330","title":"Afghan-Taliban peace talks start in shadow of twin towers anniversary","paragraph":"The talks open with an inauguration ceremony which will be attended by US Secretary of State Mike Pompeo.","entity":[{"entity_text":"US","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"State","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Mike Pompeo","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/tennis\/dominic-thiem-to-face-alexander-zverev-in-final-as-us-open-prepares-to-crown-a-first-time-grand-slam-champion-1.1076396","title":"Dominic Thiem to face Alexander Zverev in final as US Open prepares to crown a first-time Grand Slam champion","paragraph":"Novak Djokovic's latest misguided moment does irreparable damage to his public image","entity":[{"entity_text":"Novak Djokovic's","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/other-sport\/ottman-azaitar-moroccan-fighter-eager-to-make-up-for-lost-time-at-ufc-fight-night-1.1076461","title":"Ottman Azaitar: Moroccan fighter eager to make up for lost time at UFC Fight Night","paragraph":"It is something Azaitar embraces but not actively seeks, happy instead to let his talent do the talking. He has finished 11 of his 12 fights.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Azaitar","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"11","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"12","entity_type":"CARDINAL"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/tennis\/italian-open-rafael-nadal-and-novak-djokovic-renew-rivalry-ahead-of-roland-garros-1.1076971","title":"Italian Open: Rafael Nadal and Novak Djokovic renew rivalry ahead of Roland Garros","paragraph":"Nadal could play either Greek third seed Stefanos Tsitsipas or seventh seeded Italian Fabio Fognini for a place in the final. The Spaniard has a 61-6 tournament record, having not lost before the quarter-finals since 2008.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Greek","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"third","entity_type":"ORDINAL"},{"entity_text":"seventh","entity_type":"ORDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Italian","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"Fabio Fognini","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Spaniard","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"61","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"quarter","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"2008","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/jerome-boateng-sports-purple-hair-colour-as-bayern-munich-train-for-new-season-in-pictures-1.1076291","title":"Jerome Boateng sports purple hair colour as Bayern Munich train for new season - in pictures","paragraph":"L:27 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:27 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/in-beirut-a-rescued-pelican-becomes-symbol-of-hope-in-crisis-stricken-lebanon-1.1077035","title":"In Beirut, a rescued pelican becomes symbol of hope in crisis-stricken Lebanon","paragraph":"The pelican is particularly afraid of children, because they have attacked him in the past with sticks.","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/world\/uk-awards-burberry-1-8m-in-coronavirus-contracts-1.1076196","title":"UK awards Burberry &pound;1.8m in coronavirus contracts","paragraph":"“Earlier this year, we donated more than 160,000 pieces of PPE to the NHS and healthcare charities that we manufactured at our trench coat factory in Castleford, Yorkshire, and sourced through our supply chain.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Earlier this year","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"more than 160,000","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"PPE","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"NHS","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Castleford","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Yorkshire","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/government\/dubai-issues-hundreds-of-fines-at-malls-in-campaign-against-covid-19-offenders-1.1076903","title":"Dubai issues hundreds of fines at malls in campaign against Covid-19 offenders","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/lifestyle\/travel\/amsterdam-s-most-expensive-place-to-stay-one-night-from-dh106-000-1.1076619","title":"Amsterdam's most expensive place to stay: one night from Dh106,000","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/sport\/cricket\/ipl-2020-letting-schoolboy-prodigy-tom-banton-go-was-the-biggest-decision-for-dougie-brown-1.1076568","title":"IPL 2020: Letting schoolboy prodigy Tom Banton go was the 'biggest decision' for Dougie Brown","paragraph":"He said he is just glad to be involved in a tournament as high profile as the IPL, saying it us “something I have been dreaming of since a very young age.”","entity":[{"entity_text":"IPL","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/vaccine-confidence-rises-in-some-countries-but-falls-in-others-lancet-study-finds-1.1076440","title":"Vaccine confidence rises in some countries but falls in others, Lancet study finds","paragraph":"There are currently six research laboratories in Phase 3 of World Health Organisation-recognised clinical trials for a vaccine.","entity":[{"entity_text":"six","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"3","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"World Health Organisation","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/coronavirus-dubai-cafe-shut-for-ignoring-distancing-rules-1.1076629","title":"Coronavirus: Dubai cafe shut for ignoring distancing rules","paragraph":"A department store was fined Dh50,000 for a flash sale on Wednesday that caused crowds to gather on the streets.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Dh50,000","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Wednesday","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/heritage\/emirates-loto-winner-uses-dh100-000-prize-to-help-family-caught-up-in-beirut-blast-1.1076209","title":"Emirates Loto winner uses Dh100,000 prize to help family caught up in Beirut blast","paragraph":"Mr Itani, who holds Canadian citizenship, has been living in the UAE for 17 years.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Canadian","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"UAE","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"17 years","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/science\/sheikh-mohammed-bin-rashid-hails-emirati-physicist-for-winning-science-oscar-1.1076265","title":"Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid hails Emirati physicist for winning 'science Oscar'","paragraph":"L:25 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:25 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/generation-start-up-ikcon-cooks-up-plans-to-take-bigger-bite-out-of-food-delivery-market-1.1076539","title":"Generation Start-up: iKcon cooks up plans to take bigger bite out of food delivery market","paragraph":"Start-ups in the Middle East and North Africa secured $659m in funding in the first half of this year, an increase of 35 per cent from the previous year, according to data platform Magnitt.","entity":[{"entity_text":"the Middle East","entity_type":"LOC"},{"entity_text":"North Africa","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"$659m","entity_type":"MONEY"},{"entity_text":"the first half of this year","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"35 per cent","entity_type":"MONEY"},{"entity_text":"the previous year","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Magnitt","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/opinion\/comment\/my-son-and-i-were-lucky-to-access-the-best-of-us-health-care-1.1076517","title":"My son and I were lucky to access the best of US health care","paragraph":"The emergency room was full so I spent most of the day on a stretcher in a narrow corridor next to the laundry bins. Doctors, nurses, technicians and laundry workers who passed gaped down at me. It was a few days after Labour Day – the traditional end of US summer holidays – and for some reason, the place was insanely busy.","entity":[{"entity_text":"the day","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"a few days","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Labour Day","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"US","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/beirut-port-fire-private-firms-say-lax-oversight-led-to-blaze-1.1076308","title":"Beirut port fire: private firms say lax oversight led to blaze","paragraph":"Already berated for their negligence and corruption, the Lebanese authorities were harshly criticised again on Thursday for failing to secure the port properly.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Lebanese","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"Thursday","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/education\/coronavirus-affordable-dubai-schools-find-creative-ways-to-open-amid-covid-19-1.1076387","title":"Coronavirus: Affordable Dubai schools find creative ways to open amid Covid-19","paragraph":"Ms Davison said the school spent between Dh10,000 and Dh20,000 to prepare the clinic. ","entity":[{"entity_text":"Ms Davison","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/economy\/swedish-regulator-worries-about-lack-of-physical-cash-1.1076493","title":"Swedish regulator worries about lack of physical cash","paragraph":"Mr Ingves says the issue also raises “practical” questions about the role of a central bank. That’s why Sweden’s Riksbank has done more advanced planning than most of its peers to figure out how to stay relevant and how to ensure citizens don’t suddenly find themselves without access to real money.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Ingves","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Sweden","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Riksbank","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/education\/coronavirus-affordable-dubai-schools-find-creative-ways-to-open-amid-covid-19-1.1076387","title":"Coronavirus: Affordable Dubai schools find creative ways to open amid Covid-19","paragraph":"&quot;We had to set up a small isolation room, a consultation room and all of this is a big expense for an affordable school,&quot; said Shiny Davison, director of learning at Gulf Model School in Dubai, which charges Dh356 a month for kindergarten to Dh647 for grade 12. ","entity":[{"entity_text":"&quot;We","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Davison","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Gulf Model School","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Dubai","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Dh356","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Dh647","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"12","entity_type":"CARDINAL"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/tennis\/naomi-osaka-v-victoria-azarenka-us-open-final-pits-tennis-biggest-female-star-against-rejuvenated-veteran-1.1076427","title":"Naomi Osaka v Victoria Azarenka: US Open final pits tennis' biggest female star against rejuvenated veteran","paragraph":"Victoria Azarenka stuns Serena Williams to enter US Open final","entity":[{"entity_text":"Victoria Azarenka","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Serena Williams","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"US","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/tennis\/naomi-osaka-comes-from-behind-to-win-us-open-in-pictures-1.1076772","title":"Naomi Osaka comes from behind to win US Open - in pictures","paragraph":"It brought the 22-year-old's haul of tennis major trophies to three after her victories at the 2018 US Open and 2019 Australian Open.","entity":[{"entity_text":"22-year-old","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"three","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"the 2018 US Open","entity_type":"EVENT"},{"entity_text":"2019","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/tennis\/dominic-thiem-to-face-alexander-zverev-in-final-as-us-open-prepares-to-crown-a-first-time-grand-slam-champion-1.1076396","title":"Dominic Thiem to face Alexander Zverev in final as US Open prepares to crown a first-time Grand Slam champion","paragraph":"Earlier, Zverev came from two sets down to complete a remarkable comeback against 20th-seeded Spaniard Pablo Carreno Busta and reach his first tennis major final.","entity":[{"entity_text":"two","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"20th","entity_type":"ORDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Spaniard Pablo","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"first","entity_type":"ORDINAL"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/the-middle-east-framed-regional-photography-for-september-11-2020-1.1076239","title":"The Middle East Framed - regional photography for September 11, 2020","paragraph":"H:40 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:40 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/asia\/pakistani-police-chief-sparks-outrage-by-blaming-gang-rape-victim-1.1076293","title":"Pakistani police chief sparks outrage by blaming gang-rape victim","paragraph":"H:38 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:38 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/lebanese-soldiers-fire-live-bullets-as-protesters-march-on-presidential-palace-1.1076709","title":"Lebanese soldiers fire live bullets as protesters march on presidential palace","paragraph":"Tension is high in Lebanon after last month’s devastating explosion at Beirut’s port, which killed at least 191 people, and another huge blaze at the same site on Thursday.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Lebanon","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"last month","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Beirut","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"at least 191","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Thursday","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/europe\/uk-finally-launches-a-coronavirus-tracking-app-1.1076258","title":"UK finally launches a coronavirus tracking app","paragraph":"Features on the app include a QR code system that business owners are encouraged to join.","entity":[{"entity_text":"app","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/the-middle-east-framed-regional-photography-for-september-13-2020-1.1076994","title":"The Middle East framed - regional photography for September 13, 2020","paragraph":"L:25 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:25 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/environment\/working-from-home-could-create-surge-in-gulf-s-ac-bills-and-emissions-1.1077001","title":"Working from home could create surge in Gulf's AC bills and emissions","paragraph":"“Water has a much higher heat capacity than air, which means it can absorb more heat from air-conditioning systems,” Prof Al Habaibeh said.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Prof Al Habaibeh","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/government\/dubai-police-arrests-man-for-breaking-quarantine-and-bragging-about-it-1.1076697","title":"Dubai Police arrests man for breaking quarantine and bragging about it","paragraph":"The man posted online saying he went out to buy coffee despite being infected with Covid-19, police said. ","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/world\/the-americas\/us-gears-for-rising-death-toll-in-west-coast-wildfires-1.1076707","title":"US gears for rising death toll in West Coast wildfires","paragraph":"H:41 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:41 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/comment\/why-working-smarter-is-more-important-than-working-longer-1.1076442","title":"Why working smarter is more important than working longer","paragraph":"How business owners can stay motivated in a pandemic","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/lifestyle\/travel\/india-s-first-airport-covid-19-test-centre-opens-in-delhi-only-for-transit-passengers-1.1076881","title":"India&rsquo;s first airport Covid-19 test centre opens in Delhi &ndash; only for transit passengers","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/opinion\/comment\/is-erdogan-interested-in-a-deal-with-europe-1.1076466","title":"Is Erdogan interested in a deal with Europe?","paragraph":"Greece has appealed for support from its fellow Europeans as it faces Turkish encroachment into its territorial waters around the Mediterranean basin. Cyprus has seen a Turkish exploration flotilla linger in its waters for weeks. France has sent war planes to patrol the area. The Pentagon ordered US military exercises in the area as a show of involvement and, presumably, a caution against further escalation.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Greece","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Europeans","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"Turkish","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"Mediterranean","entity_type":"LOC"},{"entity_text":"Turkish","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"weeks","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"France","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Pentagon","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"US","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/lifestyle\/comment\/as-a-mum-here-are-three-reasons-i-d-never-have-a-gender-reveal-party-1.1077017","title":"As a mum, here are three reasons I'd never have a gender reveal party ...","paragraph":"A gender reveal party is no different. Sure, being with family may make the moment more special, but does finding out your baby's gender while surrounded with props for Instagram actually increase the joy of the moment? Probably not. ","entity":[{"entity_text":"Instagram","entity_type":"PRODUCT"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/generation-start-up-ikcon-cooks-up-plans-to-take-bigger-bite-out-of-food-delivery-market-1.1076539","title":"Generation Start-up: iKcon cooks up plans to take bigger bite out of food delivery market","paragraph":"The Philippines-based company opened its first cloud kitchen in Singapore last month.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Philippines","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"first","entity_type":"ORDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Singapore","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"last month","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/lifestyle\/travel\/emirates-to-resume-flights-to-casablanca-in-september-1.1076191","title":"Emirates to resume flights to Casablanca in September","paragraph":"The Dubai airline will restart flights to the Moroccan city from Friday, September 18, as part of its restored network.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Dubai","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Moroccan","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"Friday, September 18","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/google-to-block-search-suggestions-to-stop-misinformation-spreading-online-during-us-election-1.1076220","title":"Google to block search suggestions to stop misinformation spreading online during US election","paragraph":"H:37 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:37 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/other-sport\/ottman-azaitar-set-to-compete-at-ufc-fight-island-after-explosive-return-in-las-vegas-1.1076908","title":"Ottman Azaitar set to compete at UFC Fight Island after explosive return in Las Vegas","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/sport\/cricket\/ipl-2020-letting-schoolboy-prodigy-tom-banton-go-was-the-biggest-decision-for-dougie-brown-1.1076568","title":"IPL 2020: Letting schoolboy prodigy Tom Banton go was the 'biggest decision' for Dougie Brown","paragraph":"Tom Banton could be forgiven for getting ahead of himself when he arrives in Abu Dhabi for the IPL.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Tom Banton","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Abu Dhabi","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"IPL","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/prospects-for-pound-look-shaky-on-no-deal-brexit-concerns-1.1076523","title":"Prospects for pound look shaky on 'no-deal Brexit' concerns","paragraph":"Money market investors are stepping up bets the Bank of England will cut rates below zero for the first time in its 326-year history, and options markets are pricing in the likelihood of deeper losses for the pound. Excluding mid-March, the week will be recorded as sterling’s worst sell-off since 2016.","entity":[{"entity_text":"the Bank of England","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"zero","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"first","entity_type":"ORDINAL"},{"entity_text":"326-year","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"mid-March","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"the week","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"2016","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/europe\/design-guru-sir-terence-conran-for-whom-the-word-lifestyle-was-created-dies-1.1076570","title":"Design guru Sir Terence Conran, for whom the word lifestyle was created, dies","paragraph":"L:25 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:25 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/the-americas\/coronavirus-heart-damage-detected-in-infected-young-athletes-1.1076374","title":"Coronavirus: heart damage detected in infected young athletes","paragraph":"The Ohio study was not designed to identify the prevalence or risk of myocardial injury in athletes with a recent history of coronavirus infection, Mr Rajpal said. Further studies are planned in which athletes not affected by the coronavirus will also be assessed for comparison. More research is also needed to understand the long-term consequences of Covid-19 on the hearts of young athletes, he said.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Ohio","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Mr Rajpal","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/jerome-boateng-sports-purple-hair-colour-as-bayern-munich-train-for-new-season-in-pictures-1.1076291","title":"Jerome Boateng sports purple hair colour as Bayern Munich train for new season - in pictures","paragraph":"While Bayern have no dearth of star power, one player stood out during training. It was difficult to miss Jerome Boateng, who sported purple hair colour and a sharp hair cut. ","entity":[{"entity_text":"one","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Jerome Boateng","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/google-to-block-search-suggestions-to-stop-misinformation-spreading-online-during-us-election-1.1076220","title":"Google to block search suggestions to stop misinformation spreading online during US election","paragraph":"H:42 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:42 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/european-powers-push-iran-hard-to-comply-with-nuclear-deal-1.1076214","title":"European powers push Iran hard to comply with nuclear deal","paragraph":"Meanwhile Iran’s uranium stockpile is currently ten times over the limit set in JCPOA deal, a leaked UN watchdog report has revealed.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Iran","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"ten","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"JCPOA","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"UN","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/podcasts\/1-007-new-cases-etihad-flights-to-morocco-oxford-university-trial-restarts-the-daily-update-1.1076854","title":"1,007 new cases, Etihad flights to Morocco, Oxford University trial restarts - The Daily Update","paragraph":"H:42 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:42 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/health\/coronavirus-dubai-restaurant-shut-down-after-free-meal-deal-attracts-crowds-1.1076205","title":"Coronavirus: Dubai restaurant shut down after free meal deal attracts crowds","paragraph":"H:42 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:42 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/government\/dubai-s-24-hour-hotline-gives-elderly-secure-line-to-request-help-or-report-abuse-1.1077037","title":"Dubai's 24-hour hotline gives elderly secure line to request help or report abuse","paragraph":"A bilingual team will take the calls, follow up with immediate action when required and supervise the care of elderly people.","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/sport\/other-sport\/team-sunweb-s-soren-kragh-andersen-earns-surprise-tour-de-france-victory-1.1076695","title":"Team Sunweb's Soren Kragh Andersen earns surprise Tour de France victory","paragraph":"He remains 44 seconds ahead of his fellow Slovenian Tadej Pogacar, of UAE Team Emirates, in second place and 59 clear of defending champion Egan Bernal.","entity":[{"entity_text":"44 seconds","entity_type":"TIME"},{"entity_text":"Slovenian","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"UAE Team Emirates","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"second","entity_type":"ORDINAL"},{"entity_text":"59","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Egan Bernal","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/asia\/china-releases-5-missing-indian-nationals-amid-standoff-1.1076476","title":"China releases 5 missing Indian nationals amid standoff","paragraph":"After that clash, both sides disengaged from the site in the Galwan Valley and at least two other places, but the crisis continued.","entity":[{"entity_text":"the Galwan Valley","entity_type":"LOC"},{"entity_text":"at least two","entity_type":"CARDINAL"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/brighton-s-graham-potter-ready-for-challenge-of-facing-exciting-new-chelsea-1.1077047","title":"Brighton's Graham Potter ready for challenge of facing 'exciting' new Chelsea","paragraph":"More than &pound;200 million (Dh940m) has been spent bringing Hakim Ziyech, Timo Werner, Kai Havertz, Thiago Silva, Ben Chilwell and Malang Sarr to Stamford Bridge.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Hakim Ziyech","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Timo Werner","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Kai Havertz","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Thiago Silva","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Ben Chilwell","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Malang Sarr","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Stamford Bridge","entity_type":"FAC"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/environment\/working-from-home-could-create-surge-in-gulf-s-ac-bills-and-emissions-1.1077001","title":"Working from home could create surge in Gulf's AC bills and emissions","paragraph":"H:41 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:41 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/atletico-madrid-manager-diego-simeone-tests-positive-for-coronavirus-1.1076961","title":"Atletico Madrid manager Diego Simeone tests positive for coronavirus","paragraph":"Atletico's squad and staff returned early from a pre-season trip just outside Madrid after a test on Thursday came back positive. Further tests on Friday showed Simeone had caught the coronavirus.","entity":[{"entity_text":"pre-season","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Madrid","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Thursday","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Friday","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Simeone","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/government\/uae-s-updated-list-of-fines-for-covid-19-rule-breakers-1.1076832","title":"UAE's updated list of fines for Covid-19 rule breakers","paragraph":"L:28 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:28 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/the-americas\/us-wildfires-dozens-missing-in-oregon-as-weather-helps-firefighters-1.1076403","title":"US wildfires: dozens missing in Oregon as weather helps firefighters","paragraph":"The Pacific North-west as a whole has borne the brunt of an incendiary onslaught that began around September 7, darkening the sky with smoke and ash that has beset northern California, Oregon and Washington with some of the world's worst air-quality levels.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Pacific North-west","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"September 7","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"California","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Oregon","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Washington","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/asia\/afghan-government-calls-for-ceasefire-as-historic-peace-talks-with-taliban-begin-1.1076423","title":"Afghan government calls for ceasefire as historic peace talks with Taliban begin","paragraph":"“The key is in what happens next. If all sides are genuine about bringing the conflict to an end, they need to prioritise the ceasefire,” she said. ","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/sport\/cricket\/ipl-2020-letting-schoolboy-prodigy-tom-banton-go-was-the-biggest-decision-for-dougie-brown-1.1076568","title":"IPL 2020: Letting schoolboy prodigy Tom Banton go was the 'biggest decision' for Dougie Brown","paragraph":"L:28 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:28 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/brighton-s-graham-potter-ready-for-challenge-of-facing-exciting-new-chelsea-1.1077047","title":"Brighton's Graham Potter ready for challenge of facing 'exciting' new Chelsea","paragraph":"The London club were under a transfer embargo when manager Lampard was appointed last summer and have wasted little time in making up for the sanction by investing heavily this time around.","entity":[{"entity_text":"London","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Lampard","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"last summer","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/government\/dubai-s-expo-follows-a-legacy-that-includes-the-eiffel-tower-and-disney-s-small-world-1.1076421","title":"Dubai's Expo follows a legacy that includes the Eiffel Tower and Disney's Small World","paragraph":"This opportunities for participating countries are another important role of Expos. A study by the branding specialist Tjaco Wallis of the 2000 Hanover Expo found that while the Netherlands pavilion cost the equivalent of Dh152 million, it created ten times that amount for the Dutch economy in potential revenue.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Expos","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Tjaco Wallis","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"2000","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Hanover Expo","entity_type":"EVENT"},{"entity_text":"Netherlands","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Dh152 million","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"ten","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Dutch","entity_type":"NORP"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/education\/coronavirus-affordable-dubai-schools-find-creative-ways-to-open-amid-covid-19-1.1076387","title":"Coronavirus: Affordable Dubai schools find creative ways to open amid Covid-19","paragraph":"&quot;It was difficult for us to get nurses as the majority of these were employed at hospitals during the pandemic.&quot;","entity":[{"entity_text":"&quot;It","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/economy\/moody-s-downgrades-turkey-to-b2-and-maintains-negative-outlook-1.1076406","title":"Moody's downgrades Turkey to 'B2' and maintains 'negative' outlook","paragraph":"&quot;Making structural changes that address these fundamental challenges can inflict short-term pain on the economy and the benefits of reform could take years to materialise,&quot; the agency said","entity":[{"entity_text":"years","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/technology\/nvidia-nears-40bn-deal-to-buy-british-chip-designer-arm-1.1076856","title":"Nvidia nears $40bn deal to buy British chip designer Arm","paragraph":"L:28 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:28 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/economy\/indian-authorities-face-tough-choices-in-trying-to-reopen-economy-as-virus-rates-soar-1.1076622","title":"Indian authorities face tough choices in trying to reopen economy as virus rates soar","paragraph":"There have been calls for more measures to be taken by prime minister Narendra Modi's government, including further fiscal stimulus, to boost the economy. But this is not something that can be easily executed, as India exceeded its fiscal deficit target for the year in the four months to July, with a shortfall of more than $111 billion (Dh407.6bn).","entity":[{"entity_text":"Narendra Modi","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"India","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"the year","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"the four months to July","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"more than $111 billion","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/coronavirus-dubai-cafe-shut-for-ignoring-distancing-rules-1.1076629","title":"Coronavirus: Dubai cafe shut for ignoring distancing rules","paragraph":"The cafe ignored physical distancing guidelines, the department said.","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/world\/vaccine-confidence-rises-in-some-countries-but-falls-in-others-lancet-study-finds-1.1076440","title":"Vaccine confidence rises in some countries but falls in others, Lancet study finds","paragraph":"H:38 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:38 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/asia\/india-reports-record-daily-jump-in-covid-cases-for-second-straight-day-1.1076521","title":"India reports record daily jump in Covid cases for second straight day","paragraph":"Brazil remains number one in Latin America, the region with the most infections globally, for both confirmed coronavirus cases and deaths. It has posted a total of 4.2 million infections and more than 128,000 deaths so far.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Brazil","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"one","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Latin America","entity_type":"LOC"},{"entity_text":"4.2 million","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"more than 128,000","entity_type":"CARDINAL"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/willian-9-gabriel-8-michael-hector-4-fulham-v-arsenal-player-ratings-1.1076659","title":"Willian 9, Gabriel 8, Michael Hector 4: Fulham v Arsenal player ratings","paragraph":"Three different goalscorers but one provider, with Willian claiming a hat-trick of assists on his Arsenal debut. ","entity":[{"entity_text":"Three","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"one","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Willian","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"Arsenal","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/football\/salah-9-5-phillips-9-costa-8-liverpool-v-leeds-united-player-ratings-1.1076761","title":"Salah 9.5, Phillips 9, Costa 8: Liverpool v Leeds United player ratings","paragraph":"H:40 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:40 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/f1\/lewis-hamilton-storms-to-tuscan-grand-prix-pole-position-1.1076672","title":"Lewis Hamilton storms to Tuscan Grand Prix pole position","paragraph":"Although Leclerc fared much better than Vettel – he will start fifth – it will do little to improve the mood at the sport's most decorated team. The Monegasque driver was 1.1 sec slower than Hamilton.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Leclerc","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Vettel","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"fifth","entity_type":"ORDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Monegasque","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"1.1","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"sec","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"Hamilton","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/lifestyle\/travel\/london-s-ace-hotel-shoreditch-closes-permanently-after-seven-years-1.1077040","title":"London's Ace Hotel Shoreditch closes permanently after seven years","paragraph":"The company said in statement: &quot;Given the unprecedented impact of Covid-19, the Ace Hotel and its outlets will remain closed so that we can invest in significant renovation that will both refresh and enhance the guest experience.","entity":[{"entity_text":"&quot;Given","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"the Ace Hotel","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/europe\/boris-johnson-says-plan-to-break-international-law-is-absolutely-vital-1.1076320","title":"Boris Johnson says plan to break international law is 'absolutely vital'","paragraph":"“Should the UK breach the withdrawal agreement, the European Parliament won’t ratify a future agreement between the European Union and the United Kingdom,” said David McAllister, a German politician who heads the European Parliament’s UK-EU coordination group.","entity":[{"entity_text":"UK","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"the European Parliament","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"the European Union","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"the United Kingdom","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"David McAllister","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"German","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"the European Parliament","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"UK","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"EU","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/gcc\/oman-praises-bahrain-israel-move-to-normalise-relations-1.1077012","title":"Oman praises Bahrain-Israel move to normalise relations","paragraph":null,"entity":[]}
{"href":"\/uae\/health\/coronavirus-covid-19-cases-rise-again-as-931-new-infections-are-recorded-1.1076190","title":"Coronavirus: Covid-19 cases rise again as 931 new infections are recorded","paragraph":"What are the UAE's rules on social gatherings?","entity":[{"entity_text":"UAE","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/education\/mbzuai-signs-first-higher-education-co-operation-plan-between-uae-and-israel-1.1076958","title":"MBZUAI signs first higher education co-operation plan between UAE and Israel","paragraph":"The deal comes a month after the historic Abraham Accord, which established full normalisation of relations between the UAE and Israel. The diplomatic pact opens up the nations to co-operation in areas of mutual interest such as tourism, security, technology and energy, and one of the fastest growing disciplines in the world: AI. ","entity":[{"entity_text":"a month","entity_type":"DATE"},{"entity_text":"Abraham Accord","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"UAE","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Israel","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"one","entity_type":"CARDINAL"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/asia\/afghan-government-calls-for-ceasefire-as-historic-peace-talks-with-taliban-begin-1.1076423","title":"Afghan government calls for ceasefire as historic peace talks with Taliban begin","paragraph":"Opinion: US troop reduction from the Middle East will serve only Trump's interests","entity":[{"entity_text":"US","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"the Middle East","entity_type":"LOC"},{"entity_text":"Trump","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/coronavirus-dubai-cafe-shut-for-ignoring-distancing-rules-1.1076629","title":"Coronavirus: Dubai cafe shut for ignoring distancing rules","paragraph":"The public can report contraventions of Covid-19 rules by uploading a photograph of the premises to the Dubai Consumer app, by calling 600 545 555 or by visiting consumerrights.ae.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Dubai","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"600","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"consumerrights.ae","entity_type":"ORG"}]}
{"href":"\/arts-culture\/music\/hungarian-orchestra-conductor-invents-sound-enhancing-face-mask-music-sounds-much-more-beautiful-1.1076980","title":"Hungarian orchestra conductor invents sound-enhancing face mask: 'Music sounds much more beautiful'","paragraph":"H:38 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:38 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/opinion\/comment\/my-son-and-i-were-lucky-to-access-the-best-of-us-health-care-1.1076517","title":"My son and I were lucky to access the best of US health care","paragraph":"Nursing my son at home, unfortunately, I had my own medical mishap. A severe headache left me paralysed. I could barely walk. Frightened I had contracted Covid-19, I made my way to the neighbourhood walk-in urgent care. The doctor there was worried about my level of pain so she sent me straight to the emergency room or ER of Lenox Hill Hospital, which happens to be across the street from where I live.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Lenox Hill Hospital","entity_type":"FAC"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/economy\/us-budget-deficit-hits-3-trillion-record-1.1076322","title":"US budget deficit hits $3 trillion record","paragraph":"H:40 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:40 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/environment\/working-from-home-could-create-surge-in-gulf-s-ac-bills-and-emissions-1.1077001","title":"Working from home could create surge in Gulf's AC bills and emissions","paragraph":"“The twin Al Bahr Towers opt for a dynamic approach, whereby an array of origami-like sun shades are programmed to ‘bloom’ when the sun path aligns with different areas of the facade and contract when there is little or no sun exposure,” said Dr Greig Paterson, a Dubai design manager at consultancy Drees and Sommer.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Greig Paterson","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Dubai","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Drees","entity_type":"PRODUCT"},{"entity_text":"Sommer","entity_type":"PERSON"}]}
{"href":"\/opinion\/comment\/is-erdogan-interested-in-a-deal-with-europe-1.1076466","title":"Is Erdogan interested in a deal with Europe?","paragraph":"Watch out for a historic turning point when the European sanctions on Turkey do come. It is increasingly unlikely that London will match its counterparts. The Brexit split will be for the first time made real in the field of international sanctions.","entity":[{"entity_text":"European","entity_type":"NORP"},{"entity_text":"Turkey","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"London","entity_type":"GPE"},{"entity_text":"Brexit","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"first","entity_type":"ORDINAL"}]}
{"href":"\/arts-culture\/television\/stevie-lee-jackass-star-and-wrestler-unexpectedly-dies-aged-54-1.1076204","title":"Stevie Lee: 'Jackass' star and wrestler 'unexpectedly' dies aged 54","paragraph":"H:40 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:40 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/business\/economy\/indian-authorities-face-tough-choices-in-trying-to-reopen-economy-as-virus-rates-soar-1.1076622","title":"Indian authorities face tough choices in trying to reopen economy as virus rates soar","paragraph":"H:38 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:38 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/world\/asia\/india-reports-record-daily-jump-in-covid-cases-for-second-straight-day-1.1076521","title":"India reports record daily jump in Covid cases for second straight day","paragraph":"L:25 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"L:25 &#","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"DATE"}]}
{"href":"\/sport\/other-sport\/mma-star-conor-mcgregor-arrested-in-corsica-for-alleged-assault-report-1.1076701","title":"MMA star Conor McGregor arrested in Corsica for alleged assault - report","paragraph":"H:41 &#0176;","entity":[{"entity_text":"H:41 &","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"0176","entity_type":"MONEY"}]}
{"href":"\/uae\/health\/coronavirus-workers-find-comfort-in-prayer-as-churches-reopen-in-industrial-areas-1.1076372","title":"Coronavirus: Workers find comfort in prayer as churches reopen in industrial areas","paragraph":"The church said it took time to sort out all the mandated sanitisation precautions before opening.","entity":[]}
{"href":"\/world\/mena\/bashar-al-assad-s-uncle-mohammad-makhlouf-dies-1.1077008","title":"Bashar Al Assad&rsquo;s uncle Mohammad Makhlouf dies","paragraph":"Mohammad Makhlouf, maternal uncle of Bashar Al Assad and one of Syria’s most powerful men until a recent public rift with the president fundamentally altered the makeup of the regime’s inner circle, has died.","entity":[{"entity_text":"Mohammad Makhlouf","entity_type":"PERSON"},{"entity_text":"Bashar Al Assad","entity_type":"ORG"},{"entity_text":"one","entity_type":"CARDINAL"},{"entity_text":"Syria","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
{"href":"\/lifestyle\/travel\/london-s-ace-hotel-shoreditch-closes-permanently-after-seven-years-1.1077040","title":"London's Ace Hotel Shoreditch closes permanently after seven years","paragraph":"The popular London hotel has closed its doors, but owners have hinted a new Ace could open in the city soon ","entity":[{"entity_text":"London","entity_type":"GPE"}]}
